Alexandros Kapsalidis

Entry Level Full-Stack Developer

A graduate from the Department of Petroleum and Natural Gas Technology, with an extensive business experience in various fields. From my youth years, Information Technology and Software Development were my favorite fields so when the circumstances allowed me to, I attended a Coding Bootcamp to realize my dreams and become a Software Developer. I am looking forward with anticipation and enthusiasm to the new opportunities that this career-change will offer me.

alexandkaps@gmail.com

6976737850, 2107773775

https://github.com/alexandroskapsalidis/ MyProjects

Ampelokipoi, Athens

www.linkedin.com/in/alexandros-kapsalidis

in

EDUCATION

People Cert Education Coding Bootcamp Java Stream

October 2019 – May 2020 500 hrs of intensive training, organized by PeopleCert and HePIS. Developed under the academic supervision of the Athens University of Business and Economics.

Technological Educational Institution of Kavala

October 2000 – June 2006

Petroleum and Natural Gas Technology

Grade: 7.09

Thesis: Hydrogen Production from Fossil Fuel.

Grade: 10

Secondary school

Subject: Information Technology.

WORK EXPERIENCE

- O Photographer in various events
 - 2015 Today
- Shield Security Services
 - October 2016 August 2017 Security Guard.
- ICTS Greece Athens International Airport
 - June 2015 August 2016
 Airport Screener. Responsibilities: Checking the passengers and their hand-luggage.

O Brink's Aviation Security Services

- April 2009 February 2015
 Airport Screener. Responsibilities: Checking baggage, hand-luggage and cargo with x-ray machines.
- Family business (kiosk) and other occupations
 - July 2006 March 2009

Hellenic Petroleum

 October 2005 – June 2006
 Postgraduate Training in the Department of Environment and Chemical Laboratory.

SKILLS



PROJECTS

- O Team Project: A Java Web Application for private tutors. Features: Organizing appointments, seeing/inserting/deleting students, seeing student's address on a map, uploading/downloading files, chatting with students who can also login. Technologies used: Java/Spring Boot, SQL, Web Socket, Javascript, HTML/CSS/Bootstrap.
- O Individual Project: Hotels. An online hotel booking web page. It utilizes HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery
- 6 other smaller individual projects/assignments as part of the Coding Bootcamp.

CERTIFICATIONS

- O Software Developer Advanced Programming Language: Java. May 2020
- Software Developer Foundation Programming Language: Java. March 2020
- O Photoshop Course. September 2019 June 2019

LANGUAGES

English: Advanced Certificate in English, University of Michigan.

INTERESTS

Photography	Reading	Gvm
i notograpity	i itcauling	Gyiii